There has been a very interesting evolution in China
.  Over the last 5 years,
online has made a breakthrough in the luxury,
premium and luxury world.  Big brands
like Maris Frog,
L6, Porz, the
historic ones born in the 80s, 90s, and 2000s, have been
sparked by online marketing, and all the
influencers have had the opportunity
to create their own small brands and
bypass all the paradigms of
Chinese fashion because they no longer need
a major structure. Instead, they have
very streamlined offices that
simply do marketing and style, and they don't
have the entire production chain that
others have built up over the years.
Consequently, they adapt
very slowly to
market needs, and they manage to buy
very expensive Italian fabrics online
because they have markups that are two or
three times higher, not the 10-1 times higher
traditionally available here in Italy and
Europe.  And today the world of luxury in
China is ruled by these 15
influencers, for example JC, they have
also started to open physical stores,
but this is to create a presence and no
longer be simply an office, but
a tangible reality.  Yeah.